

# Bojan Tomic, Software Engineer

NOVI SAD, SERBIA · 224736@gmail.com · 0628188956

**DETAILS** 

LINKS

LinkedIn

**SKILLS** 

**CSS** 

HTML

HTML5

React

jQuery ———

C#

Git

JavaScript

TypeScript

Mobx

Redux

Next.JS

Software Architecture

LANGUAGES

English

#### **PROFILE**

Full stack web developer experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic projects. Solid foundation in data structures, algorithms, and system design. Strong record of excellent teamwork and successful coding project management with excellent written and verbal communication skills. Good familiarity with a wide portfolio of software languages and applications.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

### Software Engineer, Vroom

Aug 2021 — Present, Remote

React, Mobx, Next.js, TypeScript, Software Architecture, SPA, Planning, Innovation.

### Front-End Developer, Tymeshift

Apr 2020 — Aug 2021, Novi Sad

React, Redux, TypeScript, Software Architecture, SPA, Planning, Innovation.

## Software Developer, ElanWave

Sep 2017 — Apr 2020, Novi Sad

As a Software developer my role is to identify client needs, and problems and provide a personalized solution.

C#, Angular JS, Angular 7, React, ASP.NET, MVC, TypeScript, JavaScript, ASP.NET Core, Software Architecture, SPA, Planning, Azure, Innovation.

# Software Developer, AikonGroup

Dec 2015 — Sep 2017, Novi Sad

At Aikon as Full Stack developer I worked on real-world web applications for automotive industry.

My role was to develop new and maintain existing software working in an international team.

C#, AngularJS, ASP.NET, MVC, JavaScript, ASP.NET Core, Event Store, SPA, Planning, Innovation.

#### Software Developer, Devtech

Sep 2015 — Dec 2015, Novi Sad

My role as an intern at Devtech was to use all the resources at hand to quickly learn and improve my Software development skills while also learning about Scrum and Agile methodology.

While there I worked with ASP.NET using C#, Razor and NoSql database MongoDB.

# **EDUCATION**

# Faculty of Science, University in Novi Sad, BS.c Degree in Informatics

Novi Sad

# **COURSES**

JavaScript Course for Front-End Developers, DaFed

Exam 483: Programming in C#, Microsoft

Exam 480: Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3, Microsoft

Jan 2019

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux), Udemy

Apr 2020

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Masterclass, Udemy

Apr 2020

GraphQL by Example, Udemy

Mar 2022